# **SUSHKÓ ANDRIY**

## Frontend (React) Developer

I have experience in creating, maintaining, and promoting web applications and websites for the hospitality and restaurant industries. As an experienced entrepreneur, I have the ability to collaborate, communicate effectively with clients, and have a strong business sense. I am interested in joining a team with a high level of expertise and an engineering culture where I can actively develop my professional skills.

## CONTACTS

- +38 067 630 93 42
- telegram.org
- <u>itSushkoAndriy@gmail.com</u>
- in linkedin.com/in/AndriySushko
- github.com/ItSuhskol4
- @ itSushkoAndriy.pp.ua
- Ukraine, Dnipro

## **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React, Redux, Next
- Pug, Sass
- Bootstrap, Material UI
- Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB
- Photoshop, Figma

## LANGUAGE

Ukrainian - native

English - upper intermediate - B2

## **EDUCATION**

## Master's Degree

Ukrainian State University of Science and Technologies, Dnipro 2002 - 2007

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

O 2022 - Present

Mustache development

## Frontend Developer

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScrtipt, React, Redux, Next

Creating websites for hosts, agencies, and photographers.

I am responsible for front-end development tasks, including coding, programming, and deploying web applications.

I have implemented web projects for 3 companies.

**O** 2009 - Present

Event agency "Luty"

## Part-time Frontend Developer | Manager of company

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScrtipt, React, PHP

My own company specializes in the development of various projects in the entertainment and hospitality industries.

As a manager, I'm doing the general processes like negotiating with clients, managing the team working.

As a web developer I have a part-time job. My responsibilities were to design, publish, maintain and perform SEO optimization for websites related to the company's projects.

I've completed four web projects:

- Information portal about cossacks (2018) kozaky.com.ua
- National Ukrainian show "Luty kozaky" (2014) <u>kazak.zp.ua</u>
- Fire show "Luty fire" (2012) ogon.com.ua
- Conceptual fighting theater "Artfight" (2009) <u>artfight.net</u>

#### **O** 2007 - 2009

Construction company "Arcon"

### Civil Engineer

Collaborated with a team to design and coordinate documentation for construction projects.

Played a key role in the monitoring and control of work performance, ensuring project efficiency and maintaining high-quality standards.

## **PROJECTS**

#### Chef assistant

### HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Express.js, MongoDB

My startup. A SPA to work with technological cards for restaurants. It is created in cooperation with existing companies to meet the real needs of production. It is currently being tested in production conditions.

GitHub - <u>github.com/ItSuhsko14/ChefAssistantChefapp</u> Demo - <u>chefassistant.pp.ua/</u>